{
    "id": "9f8359a726f142cbafd976513eb8f391",
    "title": "Gap Fills Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "One day scientists will …………………. find a cure for cancer.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "can",
                "be able to",
                "been able to"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "What have you …………………. to find out?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "able",
                "been able",
                "were able"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She is interested …………………. to fly.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to learn",
                "in learning",
                "to learning"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She didn’t look happy …………………. me.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to see",
                "to seeing",
                "at seeing"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "That laptop is yours, …………………..?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is it",
                "isn't it",
                "does it",
                "doesn't it"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "It was …………………. that we didn’t go out.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "a so warm day",
                "so warm day",
                "so warm a day"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "They are …………………. in love with each other.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "mad",
                "madly",
                "badly"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He was …………………. injured in the accident.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "fatal",
                "fatally"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "You can speak …………………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "free",
                "freely"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He very much enjoys ………………….",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to swim",
                "swimming",
                "to swimming"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}